[
    {
        "question": "What school does Harry Potter go to?",
        "op1": "Mahoukotoro",
        "op2": "Hogwarts",
        "op3": "Ilvermorny",
        "op4": "Beauxbatons Academy of Magic",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What house does Harry Belong to?",
        "op1": "Ravenclaw",
        "op2": "Gryffindor",
        "op3": "Slytherin",
        "op4": "Hufflepuff",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How did Harry get the scar on his head?",
        "op1": "Voldemort tried to kill him when he was a baby",
        "op2": "He was attacked by a basilisk",
        "op3": "In a quidditch accident",
        "op4": "He crashed the weasley's car into the whomping tree",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What powers do dementors have over people?",
        "op1": "They make them go crazy",
        "op2": "They cause them to harm one another",
        "op3": "They drain them of all happiness",
        "op4": "They can enslave them",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the imperius curse do?",
        "op1": "Tortures",
        "op2": "controls",
        "op3": "Turns the person into a pig",
        "op4": "Kills",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Who impersonates Mad-Eye Moody, one of Harry's professors?",
        "op1": "Voldemort",
        "op2": "Sirius Black",
        "op3": "Barty Crouch, Jr",
        "op4": "Peter Pettigrew",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the one who killed Professor Dumbledore",
        "op1": "Bellatrix LeStrange",
        "op2": "Severus Snape",
        "op3": "Draco Malfoy",
        "op4": "Voldemort",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How are Hogwarts students placed in their house?",
        "op1": "They are assigned by Professor Dumbledore",
        "op2": "The sorting hat",
        "op3": "They can choose their own house",
        "op4": "They will be assigned the same hose as their parents",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a thestral?",
        "op1": "A half giant",
        "op2": "An invisible winged horse",
        "op3": "An old pixie",
        "op4": "A three headed dog",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a Horcrux?",
        "op1": "An object that contains a part of someone's soul",
        "op2": "Mermaid Magic",
        "op3": "An object that can reverse time",
        "op4": "One of deathly hollows",
        "answer": 2
    }
]